This is the hour of truth.
si hr tish fo uthtr the.
The break has beaten
this is the hour of truth
The break has overcome
the wide waves.
It makes me dizzy
amongst the clouds.
The prow has split
the boat is taking on water from all sides.
My soul
sinks into a flowersea of hope.
O, sketch the time and shoot an arrow
which will strike the arch of centuries
in the midst of its heartlessness
While humanity
in its most being moment
in breathlessness for the perfect life
vibrates from the string of death.
I forget to forget
that forgetfulness is bliss.
being able to remember
that memory is nothing
but that which resists to be forgotten.
resists to be
resists
resists to be forgotten.
In the treacherous quicksand
where we as friends
walked, plied
towards our land,
between smoking armoured vehicles
filled with oil and skulls,
now spins non-stop the burst tire
of the car from Amsterdam
in which you got stuck in this battlefield.
I demand reperations in the name of
Martina
Martis
Kierindongo
Felipa
Raphaela
Onofra
Ignacia
Steba
Henricus
Seintje
Gieterson
Yanga
Oleana
Wanga
Arion
Martinus
Juliana
Cecilia
Margaritha
Valencia
Bernadina
Pieterson
Richardson
Joe
Lewis
Zimmerman
Cova
Bigilia
Conradus
Boekhout
Antonia
Tomassa
Manuela
Thielman
Asjes
Hercilia
Pieternella
Celestine
Davela
Ortega
Jansen
Gijsbertha
Hooi
Aniseta
Kleinmoedig
Clemencia
Koeiman
Koyman
Pinedo
Faneijter
Obispu
Carolina
Montroos
Sambo
Paulina
Balenting
Anita
Elizabeth
Constancia
Vrutal
Albertus
Maria
Marta
Alberto
Matheus
Felix
Cleofa
Dorang