I am convinced
I took on a difficult task
by accepting to govern Suriname.
But nevertheless I go towards
the future full of courage.
And were all
the masters cruel?
Your grandmother..
How did she experience this?
Once they were adults
they were summoned to the boss.
And they were told:
you have to...
This man,
this boy,
you have to "go with him",
let's say.
This is your man
from now on
and you need
to make babies.
So if no children came...
Then they just had
to make sure that...
Maybe another man,
or the man with another female.
But children had to come.
Because that is in
the plantation’s interest.
I am pleased to announce
that I have signed
my abdication
to my daughter
Queen Juliana.
And I am happy
I can exclaim with you,
long live our queen!
Hooray!
I thank you dear mother,
that you have initiated me
in this way.
Long live the fatherland!
In my opinion,
The well being and survival
of the Dutch people
can only be guaranteed
by creating an alliance
of all Germanic people.
Song number 5
As for the Netherlands,
they prefer to say
"a little bit"
through the voice
of Teddy Scholten.
A little bit.
Everyone falls in love
you know that.
You want to be wise
but you forget.
As soon as you
whisper to me.
Listen to me.
Then you know.
This will be like
Faust and Greetje.
With Henry Voetjens
in a little cafe.
And walking in the moonshine.
I'll ask you where you
want to live in The Netherlands
Make sure you give
this some thought.
But one thing.
You cannot live in Amsterdam.
You cannot live in The Hague.
Can't live in Rotterdam.
And you can't live in Utrecht.
Those places are
completely full.
This year's increase
in migration from Suriname
is confronting our society
with very serious problems.
The government appreciates
that so many people
are willing to contribute
to finding solutions
for shelter and guidance
housing and employment.
The Bureau of Citizen Spreading Policy
plans to temporarily
house 500 Surinamese
in this recreational park
located just outside
of Stavenisse.
So we are strongly opposed
to the number.
We think it's too high.
As pastor of the old
Reformed congregation
I fear we will face
a Babelonic confusion.
Boys and girls
couple together
we know how that goes.
Stavenisse has always been
a peaceful village.
Now the peace is gone.
I don't think it will be easy,
500 strangers added.
It's an isolated village.
So if a Surinamer stands here
and things go wrong,
then there will be trouble.
Hello Saint Nicolas.
Yes, Santa sit, now.
Sit down after
plenty hard work.
Yeah like that.
Do I have a nice beard?
Yes!
You wish you had
such a nice beard!
Santa I no have beard yet..
No...
Now, Santa.
I’m sure you’d like a
song for your birthday.
Yes, who wants
to sing a song?
—Me!
Ok so come here you.
You can.
And then I need
to have a boy.
This boy, come here.
There, first I need
to know your names.
Come stand over here.
There.
Now you see Sint
from up close.
What's your name?
Maureen.
-Marleen?
Maureen?
Maureen!
How?
Maureen.
Beautiful.
— And your name is?
— Paul.
Maureen and Paul are going
to sing a song together.
We have to make
an agreement
imagine we choose
a song that you know
and she doesn't.
What do you know?
Comes the steam...
—There comes the steamboat!
Do you know this?
—Yes.
Just these two guys!
Listen carefully.
See there comes
the steamboat
arriving from Spain
It brings us St Nicolas
I can see him
standing there.
His horse is jumping
up and down the ship
see the pennants waving
back and forth in the wind.
Beautiful.
They have to be suitable
for the Dutch labour market
No illiterates.
Take a seat.
You've been recruited to
work in The Netherlands.
I have cleaning job for you.
You will clean rooms
in a hotel in The Netherlands.
On a one year contract.
Do you want this work?
Yes Sir, I do.
Very well.
And how old are you?
21.
21?
And could you
depart within a week?
Yes, agreed?
In which part of the world
lies The Netherlands?
In Europe.
What is typically Dutch?
Cycling.
What does
"The Netherlands" mean?
Moments ago,
I stepped down
from government.
I hereby introduce Beatrix,
your new queen.
Is The Netherlands
often wet
or dry?