Hello
Hello?
Are you there?
Stabilize your feed.
Did you locate specimen?
Where?
What are they doing?
How do you classify?
Does it spread?
When did it start?
Post Jesus?
Show visuals.
Ours?
Describe planet.
Dominant species?
What are they made of?
Just meat?
But who is sending out these signals?
Can we just talk to the machines?
Fascinating.
Specify contamination area
What is this?
Is there a problem?
Control feed.
Trace origin of signal
Can you block it?
Where are they going?
What are they doing there?
Control feed
Generate a version
What is it?
Transmission origin?
Continue.
Who is that?
What does it mean?
Are they allies?
What is she looking for?
Do they activate it?
What's happening?
Where is the Head?
Is that the other signal?
Define mechanism
What does that mean?
What is she saying?
Hello?
What is he saying?
Define signal
To where?
What's happening?
Hello?
Troubleshoot
Confirm your identity
State your mission.
OK
Update security
and proceed.
More vessels?
How far did they get?
What does he want?
How does time work over there?
What are they doing?
From what?
Can they break the loop?
Wait
Hello
I'm here
Yes
Wait
Affect control
Mirror species
It seems to be
displacing
through time.
First occurrence
Post Jesus.
The way they count.
Nevermind.
Not possible.
System shortcoming.
Theirs.
Rotating sphere
71% water
Different life forms
Tubes and meat
Yes
Machines
Too old
They made them.
52.3702° N, 4.8952° E
They call it
Low Lands
It's pretty wet there.
They adapt to water.
Vessels
They move on the sea.
Sorry
Interfering signal
Action failed
Uncatalogued frequency
I will try
Exctracting
Collecting matter
I don't control that signal
Another wavelength
Unable to locate
The signal is gone
It's the head
It's one of their stories
Similar system
They feed each other
Local matter
below the surface.
Aluminium
Yes
To move in their sky
Another reign
Overseas
Collecting bodies.
Yes
Impossible
Unknown
It doesn't come from a machine.
Land expansion
New habitat
and reproduction units.
She asks if it's ripe.
Yes I'm here
Sonic record incomplete
Voice missing
Broken timeline
Resistant
Moving
The future
Magnetic contingency.
It's causing a
conjunction
of other signals
The signal is too close
The signal is merging
Keep listening
too close to the feed
Feed rebooting
Action?
Was there a malfunction?
Earth
Low Lands
Viral embodiment
Migrating hosts
Exponential replication
Moving beyond Earth.
Not far.
Bodies to clean
the old world.
I'm not sure
They try to stop them
Reaching into the future.
Connect the dots as they move along
the tree trunk of life.
As the little ants that could
They say, and I translate:
Yes